{
    "id": "fc0115b4d2334a7981d5ada8ffbc6556",
    "title": "Sentence analysis: exercise",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "9c99ae8d5cd14bf88f4c409d8e48df08",
            "title": "Relative Clauses Exercise",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "He is a writer ................................... works are widely known.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "who's",
                        "whose",
                        "that"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Bring me the file ............................................ is on the table.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "which",
                        "what",
                        "where"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "People ............................................... live in glass houses must not throw stones.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "who",
                        "that",
                        "which"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Napoleon, ......................................... the French admire, died at St. Helena.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "who",
                        "whom",
                        "that"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "John, ....................................... is my cousin, works abroad.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "who",
                        "that",
                        "whom"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "The boy .............................................. fell off the ladder has hurt his leg.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "that",
                        "who",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "Where is the box ............................................ I left here yesterday?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "that",
                        "what"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "The woman, ........................................... you were talking to, is my boss.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "who",
                        "whom",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "Winston Churchill .......................................... was a great politician and statesman was also a great writer.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "that",
                        "which",
                        "who"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "Mark Twain, .......................................... wrote ‘ The Adventures of Tom Sawyer’, is my favorite writer.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "that",
                        "who",
                        "whom"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}